Introduction
------------

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which VidLii collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of the [www.VidLii.com](https://www.vidlii.com/) website.

Personal identification information
-----------------------------------

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, an email address.

Non-personal identification information
---------------------------------------

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer, and technical information about Users' means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system, the Internet service providers utilized, and other similar information.

Web browser cookies
-------------------

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert them when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

How we use collected information
--------------------------------

VidLii may collect and use Users' personal information for the following purposes:

* _To run and operate our Site_  
    We may need your information to display content on the Site correctly.
* _To personalize user experience_  
    We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
* _To improve our Site_  
    We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
* _To send periodic emails_  
    We may use the email address provided by the User to send them information and updates pertaining to their account.

How we protect your information
-------------------------------

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sharing your personal information
---------------------------------

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users' personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

Advertising
-----------

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non-personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Compliance with children's online privacy protection act
--------------------------------------------------------

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

Changes to this privacy policy
------------------------------

VidLii retains the right, at its sole discretion, to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Your acceptance of these terms
------------------------------

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

Contacting us
-------------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us.

For questions concerning the product or your account, please check out the [Help](https://www.vidlii.com/help) page.
